songsvibe.in 2011-11-23

# Privacy - SongsVibe - Download Free Hindi MP3 Songs - Listen - Play >>

**Privacy Policy Of Songsvibe.in**

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our feeds , RSS or Feedburner Feeds or giving a comment on any of the article..  
When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. We will also ask you e-mail address while you get subscribed to our RSS Email Feed or Via Feedburner Feed provided at http://feeds.feedburner.in/songsvibe/ . While if you don’t wish to continue with our daily e-mail updates you can unsubscribe via link given below in the given e-mail.  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

To send periodic emails when our site gets updated. Mails are sent once a day only and we do not spam in anyway as we oppose spam. Mails will be sent from official Google FeedBurner mail Servers

Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.  
Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

**Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at http://www.songsvibe.in/tos/. We also encourage you to go through our disclaimer page also which can be found here http://www.songsvibe.in/disclaimer/

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

_www.songsvibe.in  
songsvibe(@)gmail(dot)com_
